CPI year over year
percent change Is
it going to be
– is the PPI
inflation rate going to
be above the CPI
inflation rate for three
consecutive months in 2026
So you can see
here that the market
is pretty sure that
producer price inflation is
going to consumer price
inflation on a year
over year basis for
three consecutive months this
year Now that's very
interesting Now
what is this saying
Well you can see
it started out closer
to 25 or
20 percent probability moved
to 30 as the
initial stages of the
war in took off
And then everyone thought
it was going to
be over quickly settled
back and you can
see what has since
This is more extended
than many observers predicted
And so that's where
there's certainty so far
as you can see
on the next chart
What's interesting about this
is we already have
two