derivatives right It's the
catalyst that will drive
the performance of a
up or down And
so whereas you may
want to out some
of that risk using
a put call spread
or many other forms
of hedging now you
have direct access to
those underlying events business
KPIs macroeconomic events
where you don't need
to take on the
extra risk that is
associated with the right
If you don't want
to be exposed to
what is in well
you don't need to
take on that through
derivatives which are going
to have some of
that in it You
can go directly to
the underlying event So
I think it's a
really amazing opportunity for
the markets when we've
doing this research And
I'll give a sneak
preview I think you
in the medium term
over the next few
years we believe that
this market could explode
up to five trillion
dollars in notional volume
Now right now Cal
she is on an
annualized run rate to
do around one hundred
and