over the next few
years we believe that
this market could explode
up to five trillion
dollars in notional volume
Now right now Cal
she is on an
annualized run rate to
do around one hundred
and twenty one hundred
and thirty billion dollars
in notional volume for
this year So we're
talking about a massive
explosion of where this
total market is But
when you put it
into the perspective of
the total derivatives market
which in 2024 was
around seven hundred and
trillion dollars in notional
volume you're only talking
about 70 basis points
right That five five
trillion dollar figure over
715 So it's a
drop in the compared
to where traditional derivatives
sit today And as
you point out I
think this is an
expansion of the addressable
market that derivatives don't
necessarily give you today
in terms of the
risk profile