story technology
the innovation platforms that
I just mentioned involve
15 different technologies
They're converging And we
think that productivity growth
is going to in
the next few years
So here we ask
the non farm productivity
increase above
3 in any quarter
This is on a
year over year basis
in any quarter in
26 And you can
see there's a 42
probability Well
we think the actually
is much higher than
that And it's actually
for a statistical reason
If you look at
productivity today you can
see we're at 2
5 And
you can also see
again if you look
across this chart this
is in the higher
half of the
of this So
pretty strong And
as we have said
in the know many
times we've in a
rolling recession and this
is what has That's
so interesting