And that goes against
conventional wisdom Now
we agree that it
is going to go
up mostly because
of what I just
mentioned about foreign direct
investment and our
capital friendly business friendly
tax policies Also deregulation
is think
going to the return
on investment in the
United States relative to
that in the rest
of the That is
dollar positive And we
take this chart all
the way back into
the early 80s Why
It is because we
like to what happened
during Reaganomics And we
think Trumponomics resembles
greatly Reaganomics
And look what happened
to the dollar back
then Now it was
coming from the of
in the late 70s
But it really went
into overdrive to the
point where all the
treasury and ministers around
the got together and
said this is becoming
a deflationary risk to
the rest of the
Because a lot of
debt is
denominated was and still
is denominated in
dollars So the debt
service was getting more
and expensive back then
We think we're not
going to see a
like we did in
the early 80s But
we think the pressure
is to the